<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Search</string>
    <string name="faculty">To evolve into a centre of excellence in Science and
        Technology through creative and innovative practices in teaching - learning,
        towards promoting academic achievement and research excellence to produce
        internationally accepted, competitive and world class
        professionals who are psychologically strong and emotionally balanced
        imbued with social consciousness and ethical values.
        To provide high quality academic programmes, training activities,
        research facilities and opportunities supported by continuous
        industry - institute interaction aimed at promoting employability, entrepreneurship,
        leadership and research aptitude among
        students and contribute to the
        economic and technological development of the region, state and nation</string>

    <string name="Chairman"> Dr. L. Rathaiah, Chairman of Vignan group of institutions,
        was destined to be different, or should we say, he chose to be different.
        He was not content with just teaching. He spotted the chinks in the education
        system of the state and went about changing it to make it more effective,
        productive and powerful. He successfully altered the education scenario in A.P
        and brought about a socio-economic revolution of sorts. The education fraternity
        was so persuaded by the strength of this alternate model that they adopted the
        new system of imparting education without any reservation.
        The system initiated by this illustrious
        educationist, became instrumental in affecting a paradigm shift in
        the whole education scenario of the state.</string>

    <string name="vice">Greetings from the Vice-Chancellor of the Vignan\'s Foundation for Science, Technology and Research.
                        As contained in the very title of the institution, the focussed
                        objective is to ensure that the outgoing graduates are foundation wise strong in their respective
                        disciplines and across, confirming that they would be the most trusted performers; performers - professionally
                        strong with ethics and commitment.The title of the institution also implies that the learning process
                        in the University encompasses all three aspects - Science,
                        Technology and Research, expressed in simple alternate terms, a learner will emerge as a balanced
                        agglomeration of Fundamentals of underlying Science -
                        that is the Knowledge to accept the problem.
                        Capability to transform the Science into Technology -
                        that is the Skill to solve the problem.
                        Intrinsic values of Research -
                        that is the Creativity in providing a value composed solution to the problem.
    </string>

    <string name="Akash">Name : Sai Akash\nBranch : AIML\nSection: A\nDay scholar: Yes\nskills : Leadership, Communication</string>
    <string name="shivsai">Name: J. ShivaSai\nBranch: AIML\nSection: A\nDay scholar: NO\nskills: Interpersonal skills</string>
    <string name="Adhi">Name: M. Adhi Narayana\nBranch: AIML\nSection: A\nDay scholar: NO\nskills: Conflict Manager</string>
    <string name="Vaibav">Name: A.Vaibav\nBranch: AIML\nSection: A\nDay scholar: Yes\nskills: Punctuality</string>
    <string name="Mayookh">Name: B.Mayookh\nBranch: AIML\nSection: A\nDay scholar: NO\nskills: Punctuality</string>
    <string name="Sri_Vardhan">Name: Ch. Sri Vardhan\nBranch: AIML\nSection: A\nDay scholar: NO\nskills: Conflict Manager</string>

</resources>